<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="ESUM-AddTopology">
    <title>Add Topology Data</title>
    <conbody>
    <section>
                <xref href="ui.xml" type="concept">Back to User Interface</xref>
        </section>
        <section>
            <p>
                NPAM enables you to administer and view information about the nodes in your network.
                Use the <b>Add Network Objects</b> panel to select the nodes you want to perform an administration job
                on or the nodes you want to retrieve information from.
            </p>
            <p>
                To launch the <b>Add Network Objects</b> panel, select the Add Topology Data button.
                The <b>Add Topology Data</b> button is available in the <b>Job Details and Node Selection</b>
                step of the NPAM wizards and from the <b>Network</b> panel which is
                available from the action bar in the different NPAM applications.
            </p>
            <p>
                The <b>Add Network Objects</b> panel menu provides the following tabs:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <b>Topology</b> tab  – use this to select individual nodes from a logical view of your network
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Search</b> tab – use this to select nodes from the list of nodes generated when you Enter Search Criteria
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Collections</b> tab – use this to select a collection, or collections, of nodes
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Saved Searches</b> tab – use this to select a saved search
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                Use the relevant tab to specify the required network objects and select <b>Add</b>.
                This returns you to the <b>Job Details and Node Selection</b> step of the
                NPAM wizard, or, to the Network panel in the relevant NPAM application page.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b> In the <b>Search</b> tab if you select Managed Objects (MOs) that NPAM does not support
                and select <b>Add</b>, the node is automatically discarded by Job, as reported in this note:
            </p>
            <image href="resources/unSupportedMO.png"/>
        </section>
        <section>
            <p>When creating a NPAM job using the wizard the following behaviour applies:</p>
            <ul>
                <li>If the nodes are added as individual network objects (using the <b>Search</b> or <b>Topology</b> tabs),
                        the individual nodes can be removed using the <b>Remove Selected</b> button, which is available in the wizard action when node(s) are selected.
                </li>
                <li>
                    If the nodes are added as a collection or the saved search, there is no option to remove individual network objects.
                    Use the <b>Network Explorer</b> application for modifications (add/remove) on a collection or saved search.
                        The entire collection or saved search can be removed using the delete icon <image href="resources/deleteIcon.png"/>
                </li>
            </ul>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
